<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

    <!--==================== Messages.Message() ====================-->

    <RC_RandomStoneCuttingProduct>Due to {0_possessive} unwavering determination, relentless pursuit of perfection, and an uncanny stroke of luck, {0} has unearthed a hidden treasure while chiseling away at a {3}. The discovery? {1} precious {2}.</RC_RandomStoneCuttingProduct>
    <RC_BonusMealProduct>Harnessing {0_possessive} culinary prowess, a fiery passion for the trade, and a sprinkle of serendipity, {0} has skillfully transformed every last morsel of sustenance into a grand total of {1} {2}.</RC_BonusMealProduct>
    <RC_FireInKitchen>Oh no! {0}'s otherworldly poor cooking skills have led to a fire in the kitchen! More practice at {0_possessive} job may lead to less injury in the future.</RC_FireInKitchen>
    <RC_InjuryInKitchen>Ouch! {0} has injured {0_possessive}self in the kitchen! Practice makes perfect though. Right?</RC_InjuryInKitchen>
    <RC_InjuryWhileCremating>Ouch! {0} has burned {0_possessive}self while attempting to shove a body into the crematorium. Perhaps, {0} should be more careful?</RC_InjuryWhileCremating>
    <RC_BetterMealProduced>Woah! {0}'s passion for her job in the kitchen has led to a glorious culinary upgrade!</RC_BetterMealProduced>
    <RC_HorriblyUncleanKitchen>Sharpen your knife already! {0} has made an absolute mess while butchering an animal. Perhaps more time practicing the craft will prevent future hiccups of this sort.</RC_HorriblyUncleanKitchen>
    <RC_PredatorButcheryBonusProduct>In a slightly fortunate yet ominous juncture in time, {0} has discovered {1} {2} while carefully butchering a {3}. The Rim is a cruel and dark place. Be wary.</RC_PredatorButcheryBonusProduct>
    <RC_ElectricalRepairFailure>There's been an accident! {0} has tremendously botched some electrical repairs! Tend to any injuries or other cascading failures quickly!</RC_ElectricalRepairFailure>

    <!--==================== Settings ====================-->

    <!-- Cooking -->
    <RC_ModName>Random Chance</RC_ModName>
    <RC_CookingFailureChance>Failure chance: {0}</RC_CookingFailureChance>
    <RC_CookingFailureChanceDesc>Adjusting this slider alters the chance of a pawn utterly failing to cook a meal at a stove. (Percent chance before pawns' average relevant skills are accounted for.)</RC_CookingFailureChanceDesc>
    <RC_FailedCookingFireSize>Failure fire size: {0}</RC_FailedCookingFireSize>
    <RC_FailedCookingFireSizeDesc>Adjusting this slider alters the size of a fire if a pawn fails while cooking and sets the kitchen ablaze.</RC_FailedCookingFireSizeDesc>
    <RC_CookingBetterMealChance>Better meal chance: {0}</RC_CookingBetterMealChance>
    <RC_CookingBetterMealChanceDesc>Adjusting this slider alters the chance for a pawn to cook a meal of a higher quality. (Percent chance before pawns' average relevant skills are accounted for.)</RC_CookingBetterMealChanceDesc>

    <!-- Butchering -->
    <RC_ButcheringFailureChance>Failure chance: {0}</RC_ButcheringFailureChance>
    <RC_ButcheringFailureChanceDesc>Adjusting this slider alters the chance of a pawn causing an absolute mess while butchering a carcass. (Percent chance before pawns' average relevant skills are accounted for.)</RC_ButcheringFailureChanceDesc>
    <RC_ButcherMessRadius>Mess radius: {0}</RC_ButcherMessRadius>
    <RC_ButcherMessRadiusDesc>Adjusting this slider alters the radius at which blood will be thrown if a pawn really sucks at butchering.</RC_ButcherMessRadiusDesc>
    <RC_BonusButcherProductChance>Bonus product chance: {0}</RC_BonusButcherProductChance>
    <RC_BonusButcherProductChanceDesc>Adjusting this slider alters the chance of finding additional meat from other pawns while butchering a predatory animal. (Percent chance before pawns' average relevant skills are accounted for.)</RC_BonusButcherProductChanceDesc>

    <!-- Cremating -->
    <RC_CrematingInjuryChance>Injury chance: {0}</RC_CrematingInjuryChance>
    <RC_CrematingInjuryChanceDesc>Adjusting this slider alters the chance of a pawn injuring themselves while using a crematorium. (Percent chance before pawns' average relevant skills are accounted for.)</RC_CrematingInjuryChanceDesc>

    <!-- Repairing -->
    <RC_ElectricalRepairFailureChance>Failure chance: {0}</RC_ElectricalRepairFailureChance>
    <RC_ElectricalRepairFailureChanceDesc>Adjusting this slider alters the chance for a pawn to get electrocuted while repairing electrical equipment with components. There... may even be a secondary explosion is fate demands it so. (Percent chance before pawns' average relevant skills are accounted for.)</RC_ElectricalRepairFailureChanceDesc>

</LanguageData>
